Isaac Langley

232C Royal College Street, London, NW1 9NJ +44785474843

langley.isaac5@gmail.com

Profile

Hard-working and committed third year physics student with a proven track record in both academics and extra-curriculars. Since starting at UCL in 2015, I've developed my organizational skills by carefully managing my time between my studies and my non-academic life; during my first two years I co-founded a student radio show and led physics tutorials for sixth form students, whilst achieving good first-class results in both years. Seeking an internship in Data Science for Summer 2018. References available upon request.

Education

September 2015 – Present Astrophysics MSci, University College London

1st Year Average – **78%** 2nd Year Average – **74%**

2008 – 2015 University College School, London

A-Levels: Maths (A*), Physics (A*), Chemistry (A*)

Experience

September 2017 – Present Communications Officer at UCL Astrophysics Society

Head of communications for one of UCL's major scientific student societies; my main responsibility is the marketing and organisation of society events, including liaising with members and the wider student body through the society's social media channels and contacting outside speakers to give talks at UCL.

January 2017 – April 2017

Tutor at Newham Collegiate Sixth Form

Led physics tutorial sessions for students at an East London Sixth Form college. Acted as a mentor to a small group of prospective STEM students, offering advice on university applications and other academic matters.

October 2015 - April 2016

Producer at Rare FM

Co-founded a show on UCL's student radio station specialising in London's electronic music scene. Responsible for marketing and technical aspects of the show's production.

June 2015

Summer Intern at Origin

Compiled evidence of intellectual property infringement for online game developer King, leading to a successful takedown notice against a copycat Facebook game.

Skills & Projects

Statistical methods: Regression modelling, ti

Technologies:

Regression modelling, time series, data visualisation. Python (matplotlib, NumPy, SciPy, Pandas), basic SQL, LaTeX, CSS, HTML, Excel, Photoshop.

doestrumphavetinyhands.com – Web design project with Amazon Affiliate integration. Built with HTML and CSS.

'The Infinite *Unsquare* Well' -2^{nd} year Python computational physics project; used a combination of different numerical methods to model a number of common problems in Quantum Mechanics. Received 91%, the 3^{rd} highest grade in the course.